blish.us 2013-06-05

# Privacy Policy - Publish Us - Publish your articles, blogs or poetry and make money!

## Privacy Policy

Last modified: July 18th, 2012

This Privacy Policy applies to the services offered through the Publish Us website. If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact us through our website or write to us at

Publish Us  
500 Joseph C. Wilson Blvd.  
CPU 276700  
Rochester, NY 14627  
USA  

## Information we collect and how we use it

We may collect the following types of information:

  * **Information provided by you** \- When you register for Publish Us, you are asked for personal information, including your full name, email address, location, gender and date of birth. This data is stored in the Publish Us database and is used in providing services online on our website.
  * **Log information** \- When you access the Publish Us website via a browser or other client our servers automatically collect certain information. These logs include information including, but not limited to, your Internet Protocal address, date and time of your request, the page or pages you visited and information which can uniquely identify you to your Publish Us account (for security purposes).
  * **User communications** \- When you use the Publish Us website to send messages to other users the messages are saved in our database and may be deleted upon written request. We may also retain information sent directly to us in order to process your inquiries and improve our services. We may use your email address to communicate with you about our services or to respond to inquiries.
  * **Cookies** \- Currently, we do not use Cookies to store information on your computer. This may change in the future.
  * **Other sites** \- This Privacy Policy applies to Publish Us services only. We do not exercise control over the sites diplayed as advertisements, inline frames or links within our website. These sites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit personal information from you.

In addition to the above, we may use the information we collect to:

  * Provide, maintain, protect and improve our services and develop new services; and
  * Protect the rights or property of Publish Us and/or our users.

## Information Sharing

Publish Us only shares personal information with other companies or individuals outside of Publish Us in the following circumstances:

  * Information deemed public including your full name, age, gender and location, which may be displayed alongside any content submitted by you.
  * We believe that access, use, preservation or disclosure of such information is reasonably necessary to (a) satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforeable governmental request, (b) enforce applicable Terms of Service, including investigation of potential violations thereof, (c) detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, securite or technical issues, or (d) protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of Publish Us, its users or the public as required or permitted by law.

If Publish Us becomes involved in a merger, acquisition, or any form of sale of some or all of its assets, we will ensure the confidentiality of any personal information involved in such transactions and provide notice before personal information is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

## Information security

We take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data. These include internal reviews of our data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures.

We restrict access to personal information to Publish Us employees, contractors and agents who need to know that information in order to process it on our behalf. These individuals are bound by confidentiality obligations and may be subject to discipline, including termination and criminal prosecution, if they fail to meet these obligations.

## Accessing and updating personal information

When you use Publish Us services, we make good faith efforts to provide you with access to your personal information and either to correct this data if it is inaccurate or to detele such data at your request if it is not otherwise required to be retained by law or for legitimate business purposes. In any case where we provide information access and correction, we perform this service free of charge, except if doing so would required disproportionate effort. Because of the way we maintain our services, after you delete your information, residual copies may take a period of time before they are deleted from our active server and may remain in backup systems.

## Enforcement

Publish Us regularly reviews its compliance with this Privacy Policy. When we receive formal written complaints, it is our policy to contact the complaining user regarding his or her concerns. We will cooperate with the appropriate regulatory authorities, including local data protection authorities, to resolve any complaints regarding the transfer of personal data that cannot be resolved between Publish Us and an individual.

## Changes to this Privacy Policy

Please note that this Privacy Policy may change from time to time. We will post any Privacy Policy changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will provide a more prominent notice (including email notification of Privacy Policy changes).
